Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Cross Campus Library (now Bass Library) renovation records, 1995-2007; Accession 2008-A-133
  - Opening photos-Bass Library, 2007 October 19; Shapiro, Harold; 327 computer files (JPEG)
    - Contact sheets (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - T-shirt, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bass Library -leather samples for furniture, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dedicating Bass Library booklet, 2007 November (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Tile frieze (extra set) (Box 5–6)
  - LO1 -Door number/sign sample, 2007 October (Box 6)
  - Sample Room Signs for Bass Library, 2007 (Box 6)
  - Phase 2 Design Book 1, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Phase 2 -Design Book 2, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Phase 2 -Book 3, 2007 (Box 7)
  - Phase 2 -Book -2, 2002 (Box 8)
  - CCL-SML Renovation Phase 2A, 2005 (Box 8)
  - SML and Cross Campus -Phase 2, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Program and Conceptual Design Final, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Phase 2A - Volume 1 -2005 (Box 9)
  - Phase 2A -Volume 2 -2005 (Box 9)
  - Phase II Planning (3 folders), 1999 (Box 9)
  - Cross Campus Library -SML, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Machine City -Food ServiceRenovation, Not dated (Box 9)
  - Phase IIA -Renovation, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Before Bass Library -1998 (Box 9)
  - CCL Photos, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Publicity - CCL, 1997 (Box 9)
  - SML -Turnstile Proposal, 2006 (Box 9)
  - SML/CCL -Use Study Sample, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Furniture -CCL, 2006 (Box 9)
  - SML -Preshelving Area, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Bass Opening -2007 (Box 9)
  - Public Relations 2006-2008 (Box 9)
  - CCL Kickoff -List, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Bass Library -Reaction to Bass, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Readers Guide to the SML during renov, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Phase 2A -Classrooms, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Bass -Publicity, 2005-2007 (Box 9)
  - Phase 2A -Signs, 2007-2008 (Box 9)
  - This Old Library, 2007-2008 (Box 9)
  - CCL Giveway, 2007 (Box 9)
  - CCL Farewell Party, 2006 (Box 9)
  - SML Nave Services Working Group, 2008 (Box 9)
  - Tapestaries, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Phase 2 A -Interim Enabling Projects, 0 (Box 10)
  - Cross-Campus -SML Renov Phase 2a, 2006 (Box 10)
  - SML and CCL Restoration Upgrade, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Renovation Phase 2A, 2005 (Box 10)
  - CCL Concourse Level, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Danuta's Remarks -measures, Undated; 1 (Box 11)
- Budget material and website feedback correspondence, 2001-2006; Accession 2008-A-134
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Budget -Summary of Activity
    - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 5)
  - Contact Us correspondence
    - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, concerning Sterling Memorial Library, circa 1990s; Accession 2009-A-012
  - MAK, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SML renovation
    - Masterplan
      - Parson Brinkerhoff report, 1989 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Consulting engineers, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Cross Campus Library, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - General information, 1991 May-1992 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Health and Safety
        - Asbestos, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - General information, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - High/Wall Streets closing, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - HSR storage, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Meeting planning and notes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Other, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Publicity and communications, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Seating, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Square footage, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Unit/department reports, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
      - Background information/articles, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
      - Stack capacity, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Boilerplate, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Stuff to be filed, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Facilities stuff, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Results of air and bulk sampling, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - SML Renovation Committee (Library), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Library Space Planning Task Force, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Renovation planning, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 27-31)
    - SML Renovation Steering Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Space planning, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Current SML reno. stuff, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Furnishings, meetings, etc., 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Master Plan Study - SML, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Americans with Disabilties Act guidelines, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous documents on funding, donors, planning, etc., 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chronology of announcements, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - MDA (Millicent Abell) meeting folder, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Digital imaging -- Project Open Book, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Preservation costs memo to MDA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Development plans - area curators, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Library building projects, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Reading Room - plaque, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Library exhibit, circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sparing No Detail: The Drawings of James Gamble Rogers for Yale, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Music Library Building Program, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Romantic Pragmatism: The Work of James Gamble Rogers at Yale, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Facilities
    - Project manager, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Net square footage, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Space and stack capacity, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Con-test, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - FAS (Faculty of Arts and Sciences) NSF (net square footage) - Libraries, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous SML construction material, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous library material, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Value Engineering Report: New Music Library, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Proposed Music Center, Yale Universitty [portfolio by Cesar Pelli], 1975 (Box 3)
- ARL and grant project records, 1979-2008; Accession 2009-A-099
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044.
  - ARL
    - ARL stats, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - ARL stats - Libraries, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
    - ARL stats, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - ACRL, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - ARL stats background, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - ARL stats -Acquisition - Music, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - ARL stats -Arts -Judica, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - ALS (IPEDS), 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - ARL stats -Supplementary Medical, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - ARL stat -Ref stats, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - ARL -Annual Stats, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - SPEC survey, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - ARL Expenditures Survey, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - ACRL -2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Reference Sampling, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - ARL Web Project, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - ARL Library Material Budget Survey, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Reference Stat Sampling, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Assessment: ALA Spec Ref, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Assessment -ARL Stat Surveys, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - ARL Stats Supplementary -Med, Law, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - ALS, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - ARL Supplementary, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - ARL Stat Chron File, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - ARL stats, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - ARL Miscy Reports, 1979-80, 2001-02 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - DLF Initiative, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - ARL E-Metrics, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - ACRL Info Literacy, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - ARL stats -Stremlining, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - SQ Retreat, December 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - SQ Training, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report Stats, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report Request, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - ARL stats -Law, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ARL stats -Medical, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - SCOPA Annual Report (N. Stahl), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - ARL stats, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1996 Annual Report Request, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - ARL stats, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Statistics Notes from 1995-1996 stat process -Library and Department Reports Inventory, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - ARL stats, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - ARL stats -Monograph Accessions report, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - ARL stats backup and final, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - ARL Supplementary Stats, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports -Acq -East Asia, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Annual Reports -Southeast Asia -Walpole, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - IPEDS, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ELI Project / Mellon Grant
    - Appointment schedule debriefing for the following: M. Kamari Maxine Clarke, Risa Sodi, Beatrice Gruendler, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - RISA SOD1 -SPO7, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Fall '05 Course Support, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Lewis Assessment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Website Usability Design, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Samples/Ideas for scholarly research, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Reference/Internship 2005 instructions (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Eli /Davisoutcomes, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Fall 06 Course Support, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Eli Intro Lit Project, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Visual Literacy, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Work at Kline - Instructions, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Camtasia Tutorials, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ask!Live Info, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Instructions Group, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - RSC Instructions, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Ref Instruction, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - RSC Instruction - English, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Eli/Davis mtngs, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Service Mappings, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Goal Setting/Perf Appraisal, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Library Instruction Program Develop., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Libresed, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CCL Renovations -papers written by D. Nitecki andothers, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Communications Committee, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Meetings with D. Nitecki -non ELI, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Course Support Retrieval Info, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Eli Davis -time, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Tech specifications -K. Aydelott, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Kress Fellows Reunion Photos, Yale Club, NYC, 2004 April 19; 33 computer files (JPEG)
    - Borrow Direct survey, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Web Site, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Web Manager, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - FDC, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - SML Carrel Survey, 20010-9 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - FDRTF Designers, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - FDRTF, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - FDRTF Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - FD Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Front Door, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Information Kiosk, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - LMS: Evaluation Work Group, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Library Delivery Process Improvement, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - SML Stacks marketing, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - SQIC -June 2000 -June 2001, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Instruction brochure, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - SQI -June 2001 Program Plan Draft, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - SQI Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Goal Group, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - SQIC -June 2001 -Improvementopportunity (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - SQIC Assessment Group, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - D2C2, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Document Delivery - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - DDG Report to LMC/Forum, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - EDD/Prospero, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - D D User survey -, March-01 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - DD Success factors, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Davis/ELI Davis Grant
    - Listing of teams for the Fall 2005 for Course Support Project (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Davis Steering Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Applications for Davis positions, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Review notes - 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Davis Team
      - Emerson, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Lewis, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Mazzotta, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Emerson, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ELI team debriefing, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Public Relations, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Davis Transcripts -Fall 2005
      - Mazzotta, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Lewis, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Giancarlo, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - ELI notes, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Pericles Lewis Images, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - ELI Project
      - Farragher, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - ITS Systems, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Applications: Software, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Two disks:
      - Pericles Lewis, 5-October; computer file (RTF)
      - Lewis Examples, 5-November; 7
    - Eli Project, 2003
      - Eli Assess meetings, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Eli Assess team, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Support Team, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - ELI Praise, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Eli support General, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Eli support team survey, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Eli support team draft, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Hayden, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Assessment -Hayden, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Hungerford, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Assessment -Hungerford, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - New Haven Course Support, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Assessment, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Yokota, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Assessment, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Eli Teams
      - Faragher, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - Assessment, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Cooke, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        - Assessment, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - ELI Support Team Debriefing Script, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Davis Teams 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Goetzman, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Rubens Debrief, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Aydelott Debrief, 2007? (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Sodi Debrief, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Instruction
      - Meeting Notes - SQIC, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Activity Reports, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - ITS Colaboration, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - DCC, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Resident College, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Rando, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Other Current Projects, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Events, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Primary Sources - Colloquia, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - IG Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Instruction Task Force, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - AYA/Library 11/20, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Powerof Personal Persuasion ACRL, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Getting Started in N6, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Web vs Paper Study, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Guides forother Universities, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - ITS Academic Media and Tech, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Getty Grant
    - ELI Getty Grant documentation, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Budget -Final Report to Getty Grant Program, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Eli Instruction Group White Paper, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Getty -First Eli grant, 2002-205 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Public Relations, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Other Related Programs, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Steering Committee, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Public Relations, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Haskins Team, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ELI 1st Interview - Haskins, 2005 February 3; audiocassette (Box 55)
    - ELI Interview - Carby, 2005 February 4; audiocassette (Box 56)
    - ELI "Touch base" Interview - Ellickson (needs to be edited), 2005 January 31; 1 (Box 57)
    - 3 Â½" floppy disk
      - Eli faculty interviews -A--Hayden, 18
    - Eli Teams -Fein and Assessment -Carby and Assessment, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eli Teams -Hungerford and Assessment -Connolly and Assessment, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Eli Teams -Ellickson - Asessment -Isenstadt and Assessment, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Eli Teams -Wargo and Assessment -Hammer and Assessment, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - ACRL -Stats Survey, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ALA (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - New Orleans -did not attend, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arts Library Space Planning, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Arts Library -Gwathmey Siegel and Assoc Arch, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Arts Library -New Journal Magazine, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Arts Library Construction -Publicity, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Arts: Abu Dhabi, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Arts Library Candidate, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Arts Library -Social, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Arts Library -Kress Fellowship, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Assessment: ARL Scanning, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Assessment: ARL Instruction Improvement, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Assessment: CCL Use -Survey Money, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Assessment: Managing Large Projects, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Assessment: Non-Yale users, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Assessment: SPEC Spatial Data, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Assessment: SQIC, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - CCL Correspondence, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - CLIR Conference, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Conferences (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Eli Fall Focus Session, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Northumbria, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Directoryof CT Libraries, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Directory Listing Update, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - EMS Report, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Equipment Request, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Exhibits, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Useof Space Exhibits, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hours Update, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - LSF Tour, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Lecture Hall Policy, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Lecture Hall, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Permissions to Publish, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Permission to Publish, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Permission to Publish, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - New Staff Reception, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Permission to Publish, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Permission to Publi8sh, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - RIS banner, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Sci Quest, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Spec Survey - Access Services, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - SPEC surveyon Evaluating Library Instruction, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - SQIC Awards -CD pictures, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - SQIC -setup and gift, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - SQIC Debriefing Meeting, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - SQIC -Meeting with Alice, Undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - SQIC -Programon Assessment, Undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - SQIC Awards Ceremony, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - SQIC Awards Ceremony Photos, 23 February 2004; 60 computer files (JPEG) (Box 55–56)
  - SQIC Reference Group -Ask!Live, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SQIC -2006 (Annokerson) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SQIC Debrief, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SQIC Debrief, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SQIC Service Quality Awards, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SQIC ideas, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Surveys
    - Printing and Copyright, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - CCALD Virtual Reference Survey, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Yale University Annual Stats, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Reference SAMPLING, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - ARL Annual Stats, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - ARL Annual Stats -Backup, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report Stats, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Reference Stats -Hollys Model, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - ARL stats, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ELI Project/Mellon Grant
    - Hayden: Pedagogy and Service Support, 2003 September 24; 1 (Box 20)
    - Hayden DeBriefing, 2003 December 11; audiocassette (Box 24)
    - Rae/Farrar Debriefing, 2008 December 17; audiocassette (Box 25)
    - ELI Support Team Debriefing, 2004 January 20; audiocassette (Box 26)
    - Robert Elllickson -Eli Prelim, 2005 Spr; audiocassette (Box 40)
    - Eli Team Debriefing (no name), 2005 February 9; audiocassette (Box 41)
    - Lewis, 2005 October 19; audiocassette (Box 47)
    - Lewis T.A.'s, 2005 November 10; audiocassette (Box 48)
    - Goetzman, 2006 May 3; audiocassette (Box 50)
    - Clarke conference call, 2006 April 4; audiocassette (Box 51)
    - Kamens -mid-course debrief, 2006 September 15; audiocassette (Box 53)
    - Pictograph to Pixels/Darnel and Fisher interview, 2006 September 25; 1 (Box 54)
- Maps security case records, 1979-2008; Accession 2010-A-063
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042.
  - Miscellaneous, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Maps security, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Maps - Trip to Maine, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Missing List with evidence of ownership, 2006 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alice's notices/correspondence, 2006 July-August (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Posted lists of missing maps, 2006 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Consolidation inventory list with Smiley's admission, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Maps inventory, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Delmas Grant: Maps, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Map Collection - security puzzle, 2006 August (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Discussion with other "victim" institutions - New Haven, 2006 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Smiley - Impact statements for sentencing and other evidence, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - FBI recovery and meeting, 2006 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Recoveries and checks of maps (post 2006 listing) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Map Collection rare map inventory, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Future of Map Collection, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Towards redirecting Map Collection, 2006 August (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Environmental and security Issues: Map Collection, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Map future: Collection Development, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Maps at Yale (Report), 1987 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Evolving futures for Map Collection, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Maps reorganization, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Maps delivered (to Musto) Monterey Ave., Hamden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Invoices of purchases, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Danuta's notes, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Documents from Danuta to Harold Rose, General Counsel, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Prochaska's report to audit committee, 2005 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Communications on F.M., 2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Publicity after plea, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bill Reese report, 2005 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Notices/PR about Map theft investigations, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Lanman and Cross collections, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Universale Descrittione di Tutto I1 Mondi di Gioseppe Rosaccio Cosmographo, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arnold Collection, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bibliographic information regarding missing files (Box 1, Folder 38-97)
  - Catalog cards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Yale Maps Scanned, 2 February 2000; 60; and 1computer file (PDF) (Box 2–3)
- Administrative records, 1982-2008; Accession 2010-A-064
  - Artstor, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Assessment – Borrow Direct, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Assessment – CCL, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Assessment, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Assessment – CCL Late Night, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Assessment – Computing Assistants, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Assessment – Services at Peers, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Assessment – Laptop Pilot, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Library Assessment - Miscy, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Assessment: Mystery Shopper, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)